Catarina Claes,
we are going to expose all of the evil
deeds you have committed, here and now!
Evil deeds? Me?
Wait, like what?
Do they mean when I throw toy snakes?
Or did they find out I started
a farm on school grounds?
If not, there's... uh...
You have flaunted your position
as a duke's daughter and Geordo-sama's fiancée
to tyrannize those of lower status than yourself!
And your jealousy toward the light magic
user Maria Campbell because of her closeness
to Geordo-sama and his friends
has led you to bully her in ways
that border on criminal!
What? This all sounds familiar...
I remember now!
I saw it over and over in the game!
It's Catarina Claes's judgment event!
After having her crimes exposed
in front of everyone, just like this,
Catarina is led toward her doom ending!
I can't believe it's happening now!
But wait... the ones who judged Catarina
were the conquerable characters.
In Geordo's route, Geordo did it,
and in Keith's route, Keith did it.
They took a stand to
protect Maria, I thought...
Wait, what?
Don't bother playing dumb!
We have concrete proof right here!
This is a record of all the harassment
Catarina Claes has subjected Maria Campbell
to, complete with evidence.
I saw you bullying her
with my own eyes lots of times!
What is this all about?
Geordo-sama!
Just look at this!
This is exactly what happened
in Catarina's judgment event in the game!
My doom flag finally found me!
HameFura, I Reincarnated
into an
Otome Game
as a
Villainess
with only
destruction flags···
aimaina I my me datte guruguru mazetara
If you mix it round and round it becomes unclear
akogare no kyuu tenkai ni niau kamo ne
With an unexpected development, maybe it will look good
ren ai nara iza morase
If it's love, express it now
tobikiri no dessert
with wonderful desserts
amazuppai cho misu wa oyurushi asobase
An addictive sweet and sour mix, I'm sorry to have fun
mawaru uruwashiki koi moyou
Love is a spiral pattern that spins on and on
chotto souzou naname you he massugu susume
I need to stop and think before moving forward
otome no route wa hitotsu janai
A maiden's route is not just one!
hatto suru lucky na ima ni gokigen you
My heart feels surprisingly lucky now
itsudatte maemukina desu
And so I will remain optimistic
ai mo kawarazu ni touhonseisou kou kando wo agete
If you want to win the game of love, you have to risk it all
kiyoku tadashiku utsukushiku are to wa yoku itta monda na
It's a pure, intense and beautiful feeling, so fight for it
kitto warui happy na mirai ni gokigen you
I still don't know if my ending will be happy or not
itsu datte maemukina desu
But I will remain optimistic
Episode 10
The Moment of My Doom Arrived...  Part 1
In the game's scenario,
Maria condemns Catarina right after this.
What they say is true.
If this plays out the same way,
Catarina will be exiled all alone!
That or she'll be killed
by the conquerable characters.
Does she have a toy snake in her pocket?
If she's exiled, will she be able to
take her favorite hoe with her?
Well, Maria Campbell...
Now is the time to prosecute
Catarina Claes for her crimes!
All of this...
is complete rubbish!
Huh?
Please don't besmirch someone
who means so much to me!
Wh-What are you talking about?
We're doing this to help you!
Th-That's right. We have concrete proof!
We're all on your side!
Aren't we, Geordo-sama?
You call circumstantial evidence
like this "concrete proof"?
How Laughable.
My simple-minded sister isn't even
capable of such elaborate harassment.
Did you really see my sister doing all this?
He's right!
There's no way Catarina-sama
would do any of these things!
She's far too simple-minded!
Yeah, that's right.
This idiot could never come up
with such intricate schemes.
She's so dumb, all she could do
would be to fight her head-on!
They're right!
Catarina-sama isn't that clever!
Exactly.
What's going on?
I think they're sticking up for me,
but I kind of feel insulted...
It's true! Catarina-sama would never do such things!
This must be some kind of mistake.
Yeah, that's right!
It's not possible!
It's true that I've
been bullied since I came here,
just like these papers say.
But it wasn't Catarina-sama who bullied me.
Catarina-sama has stood up for me many times.
I clearly remember who it was
that really bullied me.
If it's what you want, I'd be glad
to name them here and now.
What was that?
Catarina-sama, are you all right?
Oh... Yeah.
Um, thanks, everyone.
No, we should apologize
for not being here sooner to help you.
Sorry we were late, Sister.
I can finally relax...
I never expected those girls
to do such a thing.
I knew they had a grudge against my sister,
but I didn't think they
were the type to act on it like that.
Regardless of how she is,
she is the daughter of a duke.
Slandering her could put
them in a precarious position.
Yes, and this list of "proof" doesn't look
like something they could have come up with.
Even if it's fake, it's very
competently put together.
It's also strange that we were all
called away on student council business.
It's as if they waited for a time
when they knew we wouldn't be there.
Whew, thank goodness!
I made it through my judgment event!
I avoided my doom flags!
Doom
DOOM
FLAG
The story in the game continues
until the current second-years graduate,
so I still can't let my guard down...
But still, I made it through my
greatest crisis with all of their help!
What a relief!
Ah, today's lunch was as tasty as ever!
I don't know how you could eat
so much after what just happened.
That's part of what makes her so wonderful!
Thanks!
Um...
I'm sorry. You can all head back without me.
I need to make a quick stop somewhere first.
Where? Do you want us to go with you?
I mean, after that whole mess before...
No, it's nothing important.
I'll be fine by myself.
You can all go on ahead.
All right. We'll see you later, then.
Okay.
Later on, I would deeply regret
not going with Maria at that moment.
Our lunch break on that day...
was the last time any of us saw Maria.
Two Days Later
Why didn't I go with her?
Warm yourself up with this.
You're rather pale.
President...
Thank you very much.
The same gentle flavor as always...
I'm positive Maria-san is just fine.
Yes...
The president...
He was good friends with Maria, too.
There's no way he isn't upset right now.
That's right.
I'm not the only one
who's struggling with this.
I can't just sit around
being sad and regretting it.
All right! I'm going to find Maria for sure!
Just stay safe and wait for me, Maria!
But we couldn't find
any trace of Maria at all.
We couldn't even find any clues.
It's been three days now...
Catarina-sama, Geordo-sama is here.
At this hour?
Did something happen to Maria?!
No, I still haven't found out where she is,
but I got some information
that I must share with you.
I'm sorry to come over so late.
Information?
First, take a look at the papers
those girls presented as evidence.
I looked into it, and I
learned something very strange.
It wasn't those girls
that came up with that list.
Someone else put it together.
And what's even stranger is that
the girls have no recollection
of who they got them from.
They don't remember?
I thought they were lying, at first,
so I checked into some things.
But it seems like they truly don't remember.
What could this mean?
Do they all have amnesia or something?
It's not only that.
They don't even remember why they tried
to do what they did on that day.
It's true that they have
unfavorable opinions of you,
but they say they never even
considered attempting anything
that would publicly damage you like that.
For some reason,
I was suddenly overwhelmed
with the urge to do something horrible
to that detestable Catarina Claes.
But when I left the cafeteria afterward,
that feeling had disappeared completely.
In fact, we're all at a loss
as to why we did such a thing.
We're truly, truly sorry!
That's so strange.
It's as if someone was controlling them.
That may be exactly what happened.
The way those girls were acting
at the time seemed very odd.
But how would someone
manipulate them like that?
It's possible if one has dark magic.
Dark magic?
Dark magic is the sixth type of magic.
It's very dangerous,
so it's forbidden to use,
and it's been kept hidden.
Only a few people
in the entire country know about it.
A kind of magic
that dangerous actually exists?
Dark magic can manipulate people's hearts,
and those it manipulates
don't remember it afterward.
What a horrifying power...
Yes.
It amplifies emotions like envy
and hatred in one's heart,
and makes one act on them.
Envy and hatred...
And since you don't possess such
emotions, it wouldn't affect you.
That's why someone used it
to manipulate those girls' hearts.
In other words, you might be their target.
Me?! Why?!
I don't know.
We have no way of knowing
who it was, either.
At any rate, please be
as careful as possible.
Be sure you don't try to do
anything on your own.
All right...
Wait... If I'm their target...
Then why did Maria disappear?
She has nothing to do with this!
Yes, but she has light magic.
Dark magic normally can't be detected,
but it's said that those with light magic
are the only ones who can.
You mean...
Maria-san sensed something after that incident
and made contact with the perpetrator,
who then abducted her.
That is my deduction.
It can't be...
I can't believe people could
be born with dark magic.
No, dark magic isn't something
that anyone is born with.
It has to be acquired.
Acquired? How?
It requires a particular ritual.
A ritual?
It can be acquired by offering
a human life in a ritual.
In other words...
it's acquired in exchange
for someone else's life.
What is this place?
What happened to all of you?!
Wake up! Please, wake up!
Why... How...
If this was the ending
that was waiting for me,
it would've been far better
for me to be doomed alone!
Why?!
A dream...
Because we were talking
about dark magic before I went to sleep?
It's acquired in exchange
for someone else's life.
That future can't be real.
In the world of the game,
the only one whose life was ever in danger
was the villainess, Catarina Claes.
Catarina
Dead or Exiled
Happy Ending
Geordo Route
Bad Ending
A
Almost-criminal
bullying of the heroine
Labeled a criminal
and stripped of rank
EXILED
Tries to stab
the heroine out
of jealousy
Tries to stab
the heroine out
of jealousy
Counterattacked by Geordo
DIES
No matter which route you follow,
there's no way a future like that can exist.
And I've made so many preparations
to help me overcome this kind of danger.
It's fine. It's going to be fine.
Sister? You look pale.
Good morning, Catarina-sama.
Morning...
Sister?!
I slept so well.
I didn't get much sleep
last night after that dream.
I feel much better now, Sensei.
Thank you very much.
That's good to hear.
Are you going to head back to class?
Yes.
Geordo told me to make sure
I didn't do anything alone,
but no one's around,
and it's not that far. I'll be fine!
This is where Maria
and I first became friends.
Maria...
I wonder where she is right now.
I hope she's not scared...
I hope she's not hungry...
Oh? Catarina-san?
What are you doing out here?
President...
Um, I didn't feel well,
so I was resting in the doctor's office.
I'll be heading back
to my classroom from here.
I see.
But Maria-san still hasn't been found,
and it's dangerous for you to be alone.
Let me walk you back.
Thank you.
Wait... what is he doing out here?
Classes are in session right now...
His bright red hair and
glittering gray eyes are so pretty.
There's one route that's really tough!
There's a hidden character you can conquer,
but he's a dangerous guy who has dark magic!
Huh?!
If you fail to conquer him,
he kills the protagonist and all of her friends!
It's a super bad ending!
That bad?!
By the way, this hidden character
has bright red hair and gray eyes—
Wait! Don't say any more!
No spoilers!
That's it!
Acchan told me about the game's hidden character
and the ending that came with him!
How could I forget something
so important for so long?!
I really am an idiot!
The student council president, Sirius Dieke...
He's the hidden character from the game!
I can hardly believe that he would
kill all the people I care about.
But if my memory from my past life is right,
he has definitely dark magic.
The terrifying power gained
in exchange for a human life...
Catarina-san? What's the matter?
Is he... Is he really the one?
Do you... have dark magic, President?
Did you use it to do something to Maria?
Dark magic?
Oops! It slipped right out!
What's that?
Of course... You don't know what that is, right?
I didn't know, either, until Geordo told me.
Maybe this reality is different
from the game's setting.
My friends are different from
the game characters in lots of ways, too.
There's a good chance
the same goes for the president.
There's no way a kind person like
you could be behind it, is there?
President?
Kind, eh?
You say that about me quite often.
W-Well, you really are...
That's just an act.
It's easier to get by if I
pretend to be a nice, quiet boy.
It looks like all of you
idiots fell for it, though.
I'm the one who took Maria Campbell, too.
She learned something
she didn't need to know.
President, what is that?
Maria-san? What's the matter?
You're surrounded by the same black fog that I saw
when those girls besmirched Catarina-sama!
She saw it?!
I should've expected that from one who has light magic.
You're right.
I'm the one behind what happened.
All to get rid of that detestable girl.
But that's something you don't need to know about...
so you're going to forget everything.
Let go of me!
The dark magic isn't affecting her?!
If you hurt Catarina-sama, I'll make you regret it!
Why would you want to—
Catarina Claes, I absolutely hate you!
You reached out to those lonely guys thinking
you were saving them, but you're a hypocrite!
Watching you irritates me to no end!
Just go off somewhere and disappear already!
I don't understand what he's saying...
So, um... he really, really hates me,
he's the one who took Maria away,
and he's the one who might kill
all the people I care about soon...
And yet...
Are you all right?
He feels cold...
He looks like he's in such pain...
such agony... that he could cry.
Enough! Just leave me alone!
Get out of my sight right now!
Huh? Everything's... dark...
You can just stay asleep...
until your life runs out.
kokoro ga tsukiru made moyase
My heart yearns for you so much
kantan ni clear dekiru
I thought it was easy to clear
koi wa game sou omotteta
To win at this love game
gururi madowasete hikiyosete
I'm spinning around and pulling you in
otosu shudai wo narabuke wo
Following along in my footsteps
naze kimi dakara igai
Why are you so captivating?
dono route erabeba saita nano ka
Which route will be the best choice?
kotae wa mienai
I can't find the answer
Bad End no unmei demo boku no mono ni nareba ii
Even if fate leads me to a "Bad End", it's fine
sou saa douse hametsu suru no nara kimi to
You're the one I want in my life
zettai ni zetsumei shinai aida to chikaukara
My love for you will never change
ubai saa nareru kakugo
Prepare to be conquered
mubou mi de muteki nayosashisa mudai makichirasu mae ni
You make me feel invincible, imprudent and happy at the same time
sono chisen wo hitorijime shitte miseru
I want to find out more about you
donna kodoku mo itami mo
No matter how much the pain is
kimi goto uketomeru
I will carry it for you
machi ukeru zetsubou mo nozomu tokoro
Even if despair awaits me, I'll take it on